[{"answer": "I was at home, I was reading a book.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Where were you, when did you hear, and what were you thinking?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Very dangerous.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "I think that's a dangerous presumption, isn't it?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "No, I think this worked out about as well as it could work out.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Actually had him face his accusers?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "People are very happy.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "When you walk around New York today, what reaction are you getting?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "I think he's going to be viewed as one of the great monsters of history.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "How do you think overall history will judge him and America's relationship with him?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I heard it in the very early hours of the morning.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Mr. Blair, when did you hear the news that bin Laden was dead?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think I -- when I first thought about it, I was sure it would happen.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "Did you ever think this day would come?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Well, I think the -- the problem is, Piers, that this is an issue all over this region and beyond.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Should we be making more effort there now than perhaps we have been in the last few months?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "We've been in touch actually together, yes.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Have you spoken to President Bush since the news of bin Laden's death?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "It seems to be, because you see his caution.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Bob Woodward, is this a spectacular triumph for Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "I mean it's about as good as it gets, isn't it, for a covert operation?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Probably does not.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Did you believe that the death of bin Laden vindicates the policy in relation to Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Well, that's the question in the next couple of months that President Obama is going to face.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "I mean if that's the case, should we speed up the withdrawal of troops from Afghanistan and get where the action seems to be?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Bob Woodward, thank you very much indeed.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "And can we apply the pressure so they will do some of the things against the al Qaeda leadership so we don't have to?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "It's a very good day for our country, but it's also a terrific day for the president who made a very gutsy, very tough presidential decision, and it worked out, and I think the country and the world are better off because of it.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Senator, a pretty good day for President Obama, isn't it?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, the honest answer is that it's very, very difficult.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "What do you think the honest answer is?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "It's a signal for the beginning of a transition, I think.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Now that he has been eliminated and al Qaeda's presence in Afghanistan seems to be massively lower than it was, is this the signal for the end of the war in Afghanistan?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, I felt pretty good about it.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "Senator, tell me exactly what went through your mind the moment you heard that bin Laden had been killed?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "No, as I said, I believe it's the Saratoga or the Gettysburg.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "And then reality sets in because I heard some commentators say this is the end of the war on terror, which struck me as a pretty fatuous thing to say because it clearly isn't, is it?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, this morning I -- it was -- I relived everything; 9/11 came to my mind.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "What's been your reaction to the death of Osama?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "IN LADEN: Well, I have not heard that any of the family has renounced their name.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "And how difficult has it been for you to be a bin Laden?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Very religious man.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What kind of man was he when you met him?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "My understanding of the Saudi society is that I'm sure they are mourning because for them it's their brother.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Do you think they will be in mourning today, or will there be members that are happy that he's now dead?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, I think that -- my understanding of the Saudi law, you can not disinherit a person who is a good Muslim.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Who do you think may have been helping him financially over the last few years, because clearly somebody was?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "First of all, I was grateful for the resolute that George W. Bush brought for the effort.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "When you first heard that bin Laden was dead, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Well, I think I join Andy and probably every American saying it's been a gratifying 24 hours.", "docId": "110502pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "How do you see the next few months playing out now that we've actually seen the back of him?", "qSentId": 414}]